https://www.garryheath.com/privacy

Privacy
Heath Investment Properties LLC (operating as GarryHeath.com) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to GarryHeath.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using GarryHeath.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
GarryHeath.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. GarryHeath.com also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by GarryHeath.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by GarryHeath.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of GarryHeath.com Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through GarryHeath.com public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: GarryHeath.com does not read any of your private online communications.
GarryHeath.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from GarryHeath.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. GarryHeath.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of GarryHeath.com and GarryHeath.com family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
GarryHeath.com collects and uses your personal information to operate GarryHeath.com Web site and deliver the services you have requested. GarryHeath.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from GarryHeath.com and its affiliates. GarryHeath.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
GarryHeath.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. GarryHeath.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, GarryHeath.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
GarryHeath.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
GarryHeath.com keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit, in order to determine what GarryHeath.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within GarryHeath.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
GarryHeath.com Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GarryHeath.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Deloreshorn.com and Scottswalk.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The GarryHeath.com Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize GarryHeath.com pages, or register with GarryHeath.com site or services, a cookie helps GarryHeath.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same GarryHeath.com Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use GarryHeath.com features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of GarryHeath.com services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
GarryHeath.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. GarryHeath.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
GarryHeath.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. GarryHeath.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how GarryHeath.com is protecting your information.
Contact Information
GarryHeath.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that GarryHeath.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact GarryHeath.com at info@GarryHeath.com, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Last update: March 18, 2013
Privacy & Cookies: This site uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to their use.
To find out more, including how to control cookies, see here:
Our Privacy Policy
Business NewsCallMiner Launches a New Model for Operationalizing Speech Analytics – Wonderfully Curated News - RegisterThe taxman - Opinion - Business RecorderShowing ROI for your CX efforts - Customer ThinkBusiness Analyst - SooTodayNon fungible tokens gaining global crypto attention - Irish Tech NewsPackaging Automation Market Research by 2020 – Top Countries Data, Key Players, Industry Revenue, Demand Status and Investments Plans Forecast to 2024 - The Daily ChronicleSeven running for Apple Valley City Council | Free - ECM PublishersBest Practices for Acquiring a Business After COVID-19 - Middle Market Growth Web Hosting Plans
Residential Rentals
Make a payment
Privacy
Terms of Use
© Copyright 2019 Garry C Heath
